question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, you can upgrade the &quot;Apothicon Servant&quot; in the &quot;Shadows Of Evil&quot; map.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
